Bridget McCavanagh Curriculum Vitae

Overview

I have worked my way from bartender to bar manager and done multiple jobs inbetween. My aim is to obtain a bartending position in an establishment where I can utilise my 5 years of bartending and cocktail experience to entertain guests while preparing stunning custom cocktails and beverages. I have an outgoing attitude, an eye for detail and understand the importance of bar safety and cleanliness. I am ideally looking for a place that has a collaborative work environment, somewhere where I can take my bartending skills to the next level.

Accreditations and Qualifications

Relevant qualifications:

• RSA (2014)

Current qualifications:

- Level 2 & Level 3 Diploma in Fitness Instruction and Personal Training equivalent to Australian TAFE Level III & IV (2015)
- Gym Based Boxing, Circuit Training, Studio Cycling and Sports Nutrition (2015)
- RSA (2014)
- Foundation Degree in Dance and Dance Teaching UCLAN (2014)
- Foundation Degree in Chemistry University of Glasgow (2013)
- The National Pool Lifeguard Qualification (NPLQ) (2012)
- Foundation Degree in Dance and Musical Theatre The London Studio Centre (2012)
- Scottish High School Qualifications

Experience

The Corinthian Club 2012-2014

Bar Manager

The Corinthian Club is a group of bars, restaurants and a casino in Glasgow. I managed a team of staff in the Champagne and Whisky Cocktail Bars, ensuring a consistently high standard of customer service.

- Managing 10+ staff over 10+ hour shifts
- Rostering
- Stock take & Ordering
- Process & procedure creation
- Cocktail creation
- Other bar duties as required

The Jolly Botanist

2015-2015

Bar Supervisor

The Jolly Botanist is a specialty gin cocktail bar focused on martini's.

- Managing staff
- Rostering
- Training
- Bartending & Mixology
- Cocktail creation
- Other bar duties as required

Phone: 0466 265 845

Email: blmccavanagh@gmail.com

Bridget McCavanagh Curriculum Vitae

Independent Events

2014-2018

Administration Manager & Bartender

Independent Events is an event company that provides bar services for large scale festivals and events around Australia.

- Coordination and facilitation of hundreds of staff during large scale events
- Management of RSA Officers
- Bartending
- · Other bar duties as required

Howlings 2015-2015

Bartender

Howlings is a generalist bar in Perth CBD focused on the corporate crowd.

- Bartending and table service
- Performing FOH tasks
- Corporate events & private functions preparation and FOH/bartending
- Other bar duties as required

Orchid 2010-2011

Bartender

Orchid is the number one cocktail bar in the north of Scotland.

- Bartending & Mixology
- Cocktail creation
- Beverage recommendations based on palate & cuisine choices
- Other bar duties as required

Telegram Coffee 2015-2016

Front of House

Telegram Coffee is a high-volume café in Perth CBD.

- Providing fast, friendly and professional service
- Working In a café providing 700+ coffees a day
- Maintaining a clean working environment during peak periods

Freelance Work 2014-2019

Artist Liaison Manager

My freelance work covered a range of music events across WA, providing hospitality and catering services for overseas artists like Fatboy Slim & Post Malone.

- Venue preparation for concerts
- 24/7 availability for requests or requirements
- Logistics management; Arranging hotels, transport, restaurants and catering
- Ordering and preparing riders
- Highest professional standards was a large part of this role when dealing with named artists.

Phone: 0466 265 845

Email: blmccavanagh@gmail.com

Bridget McCavanagh Curriculum Vitae

Exolvo Performance Personal Training

2015-Present

Personal Trainer

I am currently a personal trainer focusing on technical development and exercise for mental health management.

- All fitness based activities
 - Nutrition
 - Programming
 - o Technical review of body movement
- All other aspects of running a business
 - o Accounting, Admin, Scheduling, Forecasting

Referees

Luke Arnold

Owner - Telegram Coffee Phone: 0400 911 977

Elliott Denney

Manager - Plus Fitness Mount Lawley & Melville

Phone: 0420 883 171

David Toby

Director - Pathfinder Alliance

Phone: 0450 442 112

Email: blmccavanagh@gmail.com

Phone: 0466 265 845